sitaphal.com 2019-10-15

# Sitaphal Privacy Policy | Sitaphal.com

You seem to be using a Browser Extension that Blocks Tracking. Please disable Adblocker so that you can earn Extra Cashback from Sitaphal.com

## Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all the information, including contact detail, collected about you by the Sitaphal. As a responsible Organization, we do our best to protect User privacy, Personal information and their data. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully in order to understand how the data is maintained on our system.

## Information Collected

### Personal Information You Provide

You can visit Sitaphal Website/ App and browse for which you need not provide any information about yourself. You remain an anonymous visitor. Sitaphal only ask you for different information when you register for certain Services, access various content or features.

When you log in to Sitaphal.com using Facebook or Google+ account, only with your consent, we will collect your email id and basic profile information to complete the Registration process. Apart from that no other information, whether personal or non-personal, if any, associated with the account are captured. Except your email ID (which is kept confidential), the information collected by the website is solely at users’ choice and can be updated by the user anytime after logging in from their Dashboard. No private information like Services used, Purchases made or Credits earned, etc. will be shown to public. The users have the ability to access and edit their personal/ public profile information that they want to display on our website.

When you engage in certain activities on the Website/ App, such as entering a promotional activity, requesting information about our services, email us with questions or applying for a job, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is always optional for you to get engaged in such Identification Activity. And if you choose to take part in such Identification Activity, you may need to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, email address, date of birth, occupation, mailing address, mobile number and/ or telephone number.

When you order certain products or services, you may be asked to provide us with certain financial information, including your credit card or debit card number, expiry date and authentication codes or other related information. Depending on the activity, the information we ask you to provide may be mandatory or voluntary. In case you are not willing to provide the mandatory information required for any particular activity, you may not be permitted to take part in that activity.

We also collect some information like user favorite stores, categories, feedback, etc. to make our service and user experience better. We may use your feedback to improve our website/ app, offerings, for marketing and promotions and use them to tell others about your services.

In addition, if you send any information or a product to another person, we may store yours and the recipient’s personal information. We may allow the other person to access the information which we have sent him/ her on your request. We may also use your personal information to accomplish administrative tasks, troubleshoot and resolve dispute and contact you.

We assure you that the information collected from you is exclusively related to our dealings with you. And will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by the law of the land or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

### Information Automatically Collected

We store the user IP Address and collect Users location point (longitude, latitude), Locality and City to analyze the trends to make better service and that can be sometimes used to derive your general geographic location.

We use cookies to store your browsing information each time you visit any page on our website. These are used to keep track of keyword searches you do while using Sitaphal.com, as well as your surfing behaviour on this website and other websites you may visit. This information is used to show you the Deals, Cashback offers, Advertisements tailored to your interests on this website, and/or to maintain track of your response to each Ad. No personal information about you is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by our website and, as a result; none can be passed to any third party.

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. You may refuse to accept cookies by changing the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the cookies and in case if you haven't changed your computer's settings, your browser automatically allows them. However, if you prefer to refuse cookies or delete your browser cookies or disable them entirely, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. This may also significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non-functional or inaccessible. Therefore, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

## Storing credit/debit card Information

We do not store your financial information, like debit card or credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or any other related information with us. However, for convenience in future transaction, if you may opt to save this information it gets saved on PayU PCI-DSS Compliant secured platform.

## Use of Information

We use the payment related financial information collected from you, with your consent, to complete any particular transaction or fulfilling some service (e.g., buying a deal) or as otherwise required by law. 

### And generally use other information to:

  1. Fulfill your requests for services and information that includes sending you regular electronic newsletters with the latest offers & updates, complete purchase transaction, update your transaction record, resolve your queries and complete your other requests. User can any time unsubscribe from receiving the Notifications/ emails. 
  2. Provide access to participate in activities such as contests, surveys and promotional offers.
  3. Facilitate you with special promotional offers and deals on behalf of our affiliate Merchants 
  4. Phone Number Verification while Redeeming Sitaphal Credits or Buying Local Deals. User can change their phone number anytime by verifying another phone number.
  5. Prevent illegal or prohibited activities (in case any abuse in accordance with Sitaphal Terms of Use).
  6. For any other purposes, disclosed to you at the time we collect your information with your consent.

## Disclosure of Information

We will not share any of your information with other parties except as provided below:

  1. We may share only your full name with our Merchant with whom we have an association and whose deal you have purchased. We share this information with them in order to help them identify you to provide the services you have opted for.
  2. We may share your information with third parties only if required to do so by law, with the court’s order, if requested by any government or law enforcement authority.

At Sitaphal.com, we respect your Privacy and under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share any of your information that we have collected from you to third parties for any purposes without your consent.

## Protection of Information

We're committed to protecting your personal and non-personal information. The access to your personal information is limited to only to selected personnel and is stored on secure servers. Therefore, we ensure that your information is safe after it is transmitted to us. However, no such transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure and Sitaphal assumes no liability whatsoever for any such data loss. It is advisable to adhere to the following measures:

  1. Keep your password or other access to your information secret.
  2. Ensure no-one else uses your Computer or other Devices when you "signed in" to the Sitaphal account.
  3. Always sign out from your Account when not using Sitaphal in case if you are using other computer or mobile device or browser.

## Payment Security

All payments on Sitaphal are done through PayU Gateway following PCI-DSS compliance standards, which is the highest levels of transaction security, currently available on the Internet. It uses the best encryption technology to protect your card information while securely completing the payment process. So, no need to worry about security!

## Disclaimer

Please note that Sitaphal Website/ App may contain links to other websites and/ or services. If you click on any of those links, you will be leaving Sitaphal Website/ App and visit the third party websites. We are not liable for any of the privacy practices followed by those websites. So it is recommended that you read the privacy policy & Terms of Use of each website before you use them.

We will review our Privacy Policy when necessary and may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. The revisions made will be effective immediately upon being posted on the Website and provide a notification alert. It is advisable that you visit this page on receiving the notification to make yourself aware of the latest version of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website once the effectiveness of such revisions will be considered your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have queries regarding Sitaphal.com Privacy Policy, please write us [support@sitaphal.com](mailto:support@sitaphal.com) or Fill the [Contact Us Form](https://www.sitaphal.com/contact).
